

#### DEVOPS ENGINEER · SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

1307 West University Ave., Champaign IL 61821

□ (850) 461-8381 | ■ harrisongtotty@gmail.com | ♣ harrisontotty.github.io | ☑ HarrisonTotty | ☐ harrisont

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

## Summary.

Current Site Reliability Engineer at start-up company Kasa. 7+ years experience specializing in the backend development, infrastructure automation, and computer hacking/security. Super nerd who loves Vim, Linux and OS X and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

## Work Experience

Wolfram Research, Inc.

Champaign, IL

DevOps Engineer Apr 2018 - Present

- Provisioned an easily managable hybrid infrastructure (Amazon AWS + On-premise) utilizing IaC (Infrastructure as Code) tools like Ansible, Packer and Terraform.
- Built fully automated CI/CD pipelines on CircleCI for containerized applications using Docker, AWS ECR and Rancher.
- Designed an overall service architecture and pipelines of the Machine Learning based Fashion Tagging API SaaS product with the micro-services architecture.
- Implemented several API microservices in Node.js Koa and in the serverless AWS Lambda functions.
- Deployed a centralized logging environment (ELK, Filebeat, CloudWatch, S3) which gather log data from docker containers and AWS resources.
- Deployed a centralized monitoring environment(Grafana, InfluxDB, CollectD) which gather system metrics as well as docker run-time metrics.

Wolfram Research, Inc. Champaign, IL

Web Systems Administrator

Dec 2016 - Apr 2018

- Implemented RESTful API server for car rental booking application (CARPLAT in Google Play).
- Built and deployed overall service infrastructure utilizing Docker container, CircleCI, and several AWS stack(Including EC2, ECS, Route 53, S3, CloudFront, RDS, ElastiCache, IAM), focusing on high-availability, fault tolerance, and auto-scaling.
- · Developed an easy-to-use Payment module which connects to major PG(Payment Gateway) companies in Korea.

Wolfram Research, Inc.

Champaign, IL

WEB SYSTEMS INTERN

Sep 2016 - Dec 2016

- Lead engineer on agent-less backtracking system that can discover client device's fingerprint(including public and private IP) independently of the Proxy, VPN and NAT.
- Implemented a distributed web stress test tool with high anonymity.
- Implemented a military cooperation system which is web based real time messenger in Scala on Lift.

#### **Tallahassee Community College**

Tallahassee, FL

MATHEMATICS AND TECHNOLOGY TUTOR

May 2016 - Aug 2016

- Developed in Cocos2d-x an action puzzle game(Dragon Buster) targeting U.S. market.
- Implemented API server which is communicating with game client and In-App Store, along with two other team members who wrote the game logic and designed game graphics.
- Won the 2nd prize in final evaluation.

### Honors & Awards

#### INTERNATIONAL

2018	Finalist, DEFCON 26th CTF Hacking Competition World Final	Las Vegas, U.S.A
2017	Finalist, DEFCON 25th CTF Hacking Competition World Final	Las Vegas, U.S.A
2014	Finalist, DEFCON 22nd CTF Hacking Competition World Final	Las Vegas, U.S.A
2013	Finalist, DEFCON 21st CTF Hacking Competition World Final	Las Vegas, U.S.A
2011	Finalist, DEFCON 19th CTF Hacking Competition World Final	Las Vegas, U.S.A

#### DOMESTIC

2015	<b>3rd Place</b> , WITHCON Hacking Competition Final	Seoul, S.Korea
2017	Silver Prize, KISA HDCON Hacking Competition Final	Seoul, S.Korea
2013	Silver Prize, KISA HDCON Hacking Competition Final	Seoul S Korea

## **Presentation**

#### **DevFest Seoul by Google Developer Group Korea**

Seoul, S.Korea

PRESENTER FOR < HOSTING WEB APPLICATION FOR FREE UTILIZING GITHUB, NETLIFY AND CLOUDFLARE>

Nov. 2017

- Introduced the history of web technology and the JAM stack which is for the modern web application development.
- · Introduced how to freely host the web application with high performance utilizing global CDN services.

#### 6th CodeEngn (Reverse Engineering Conference)

Seoul, S.Korea

Jul. 2012

Presenter for <DEFCON 20TH: The way to go to Las Vegas>

· Introduced CTF(Capture the Flag) hacking competition and advanced techniques and strategy for CTF

## Writing

FOUNDER & WRITER

#### A Guide for Developers in Start-up

Facebook Page

Jan. 2015 - PRESENT

• Drafted daily news for developers in Korea about IT technologies, issues about start-up.

## **Program Committees**

2016 **Problem Writer**, 2016 CODEGATE Hacking Competition World Final

S.Korea

2013 Organizer & Co-director, 1st POSTECH Hackathon

S.Korea

## Education

### **Tallahassee Community College**

Tallahassee, FL

ASSOCIATES OF SCIENCE

Jan 2015 - Jan 2016

• Graduated honors with 4.0 GPA.

# **Extracurricular Activity**

#### PoApper (Developers' Network of POSTECH)

Pohang, S.Korea

CORE MEMBER & PRESIDENT AT 2013

Jun. 2010 - Jun. 2017

- · Reformed the society focusing on software engineering and building network on and off campus.
- Proposed various marketing and network activities to raise awareness.

#### PLUS (Laboratory for UNIX Security in POSTECH)

Pohang, S.Korea

МЕМВЕГ

Sep. 2010 - Oct. 2011

- Gained expertise in hacking & security areas, especially about internal of operating system based on UNIX and several exploit techniques.
- Participated on several hacking competition and won a good award.
- Conducted periodic security checks on overall IT system as a member of POSTECH CERT.
- Conducted penetration testing commissioned by national agency and corporation.